diggstars.com 2011-01-04

# DiggStars Terms and Conditions

**PRIVACY POLICY**

DiggStars we may collect personal information such as; email addresses when individuals register to use our web sites, submit information to the web site or submit questions via the website. Any interaction a user has with the DiggStars web site, web sites and associated services may result in the capture of some information necessary to process and complete the request and ensure the development and enhancement of future services. 

DiggStars collects and collates information from sources all over the internet. This information is then stored in the DiggSstars databases. This information is then used for statistical analysis in order to determine usage patterns of content. We share this information with our web site users and third parties. 

During usage of our sites we may also collect users IP addresses and information about the users of our services. By using IP addresses we can resolve problems with our network and servers to ensure the optimum level of service to legitimate users. We reserve the right to use IP and user information to prevent and deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. Other information we may collect includes, referring URLS and browser types. We will not share personal information, unless in aggregate form, about our users with any third party unless required to do so by law. 

Our site may require you to store cookies (small text files) on your computer. We use cookies to enhance and enrich the level of service we can offer you. By using cookies we can prevent you from seeing repetitive content that shows the same information, eg, pop up ads and registration requests. Most browsers accepts cookies automatically, but in some cases you may need to enable cookies in your browser options, to ensure you can access all DiggStars content. 

Our website and services contains links to third party websitesa and software. DiggStars are in no way responsible for privacy practices or content on these external site. Please review the privacy policies of all third party destination websites in order to understant their practices regarding privacy and information collection. 

Our services are intended only for persons of the age of 13 years and above. If you are under 13 years old then you are prohibited from using DiggStars websites and services. By using our services you represent and warrant to us that you are 13 years of age or older. 

ScarlettPress is the DiggStars adult channel and is intended solely for person 18 years of age and oldder. If you are under the age of 18 you may not access or use our service. By using our service you represent and warrant to us that you are 18 years of age or older. 

DiggStars website, associated websites and services may send emails to you if you have indicated a preference to receive offers, news, updates and other information from us. You can unsubscribe from these services at any time by editing your details on your account profile page found at, users.DiggStars.com/userid? 

DiggStars privacy policy is subject to change without notice. Should our privacy policy change we will post a notice on our webster in our to make our users aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances it will be disclosed to third parties. 

DiggStars is working hard to offer a transparent policy regarding privacy. We are always keen to hear from our users regarding how we may improve, or answer questions and queries that some users may have. DiggStars and associated companies or services will not be liable for ay damage, accidental, consequential, or punitive relating to the practices and conditions descibed in the Privacy Policy 

DiggStars internet services have been designed and developed to offer usefull information and services to the internet public. We welcome you to our site and invite your feedback.
